Morgan Stanley

Farmington, UT 84025 | 801-726-6508 | morganpstanley@gmail.com Github | Website | LinkedIn

JUNIOR DEVELOPER

Experienced in Ruby on Rails and JavaScript-based programming with a strong background in design and typography. Focused on team-driven results with an emphasis on good communication. Enjoy problem-solving and understanding systems. Continuously seek improvement through feedback.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Javascript, React, Ruby, Rails, SQL, HTML, CSS, Adobe Illustrator

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

ChessBattery.com - Github | Website

React | HTML + CSS

An app that teaches basic chess openings and principles.

- Uses <u>chessground</u> and <u>chess.js</u> for chess pieces and logic, and <u>stockfish.js</u> to allow users to play a computer of chosen difficulty.
- Displays the user's opening choice, and any information on the current positions and moves, if available.
- Uses stockfish.js to evaluate the position and shows the evaluation on a bar to the right of the board.

Stocker - Github

React + Redux | Ruby on Rails | HTML + CSS

An app that tracks user-selected stocks in real-time.

- Connected to Finnhub Stock API and uses a Websocket to keep stock prices up-to-date
- Allows users to input a buy price to track the gain/loss of their investments and their portfolio as a whole

Pro Lift - Github

JavaScript | Ruby on Rails | HTML + CSS

Allows users to log and track workout data, watch exercise technique videos, and look at what days of the current month they've worked out.

Uses Date() to create a calendar and highlight the current date and any date that matches a logged workout.

EXPERIENCE

Costco Wholesale

Bountiful, UT

Stocker

May 2015 - June 2019

- Made sure items on the floor were well-stocked and organized. Was often asked to take charge when reorganizing
 items on the floor to create a cohesive and natural flow to lead members to what they were looking for as well as our
 focus items. Management was comfortable leaving me in charge of a key area for several months after my boss was
 promoted.
- Bountiful Costco Employee of the Month April 2016

FedEx Ground

Salt Lake City, UT

Load Coach/Package Handler Trainer

June 2014 - August 2016

- Supervised and trained package handlers to efficiently and safely carry out their responsibilities. Oversaw eight-12
 package handlers and over 1200 packages an hour packaged safely in trailers. Our side was constantly ranked in top
 one-two out of 16 in hub for overall performance.
- SLC North Hub Employee of the Month June 2015

Package Handler

May 2012 - June 2014

- Loaded trailers with packages quickly and efficiently. Averaged between 380-420 boxes/hour. Loaded trailers 15-20% faster and 2-5% fuller than average trailer, which resulted in decrease in damaged boxes due to overflowing trailers. Resulting work was often displayed to new hires as an example of good loading technique.
- SLC North Hub Employee of the Month Dec 2014

EDUCATION

Flatiron School

Farmington, Utah

Online Full Stack Web Development, Ruby on Rails and JavaScript program

June 2019 - August 2020

Weber State University

Ogden, Utah

Completed 74 credits towards Bachelors of Business Administration Recipient of Weber State University Emerging Leader Scholarship